{
    "id": "e141fb7984634d01a5b39187e87aaaad",
    "title": "Despite, in spite of, however, although",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8f52c040507b446899f7e6187c86c4a7",
            "title": "Despite, In Spite Of, However, Although",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We went out ....................... the rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in spite",
                        "in spite of",
                        "despite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She went on working ……………….. it was raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in spite of",
                        "although",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She went to work ………………… the fact that it was a holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "in spite of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. she didn’t like the cutlet, I enjoyed it very much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had invited him ………………….., he didn’t come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "though",
                        "however"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was fun, ………………… dangerous.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was late ………………. everybody else was on time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "despite",
                        "however"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… I was late, everybody else was on time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They managed to do it, ………………….. I was not there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "although",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went ………………… I had not been invited.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "although",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}